<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>paglaadmin &#8211; Bein Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://bein.online.mills.edu/author/paglaadmin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://bein.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:30:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>10 years of K-pop megastars BTS: Five things to know</title>
		<link>https://bein.online.mills.edu/10-years-of-k-pop-megastars-bts-five-things-to-know/</link>
					<comments>https://bein.online.mills.edu/10-years-of-k-pop-megastars-bts-five-things-to-know/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bein.online.mills.edu/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Seoul this week marks 10 years of megastars BTS, the supergroup credited with bringing K-pop into the global mainstream and generating billions of dollars for the South Korean economy. They&#8217;ve been called &#8220;icons of progressive globalism&#8221;, were once South Korean presidential envoys, and have done everything from Korean Air in-flight safety videos to campaigning for]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seoul this week marks 10 years of megastars BTS, the supergroup credited with bringing K-pop into the global mainstream and generating billions of dollars for the South Korean economy.</p>
<p>They&#8217;ve been called &#8220;icons of progressive globalism&#8221;, were once South Korean presidential envoys, and have done everything from Korean Air in-flight safety videos to campaigning for UNICEF.</p>
<p>At heart, however, they&#8217;re entertainers. Here, AFP breaks down what you need to know about BTS:</p>
<p>Who are BTS?<br />
After debuting on 13 June, 2013, the septet went on to become the first all-South Korean act to dominate the US and UK charts, raking in billions of dollars and building a global fandom, known as ARMY, in the process.</p>
<p>Their embrace of social media meant they barely missed a beat during the pandemic, using direct engagement with fans online to cement their position as world&#8217;s biggest and most influential boy band.</p>
<p>Despite earlier breakthrough Korean hits like Psy&#8217;s ‘Gangnam Style’, BTS are widely credited with bringing K-pop into the mainstream in the US.</p>
<p>&#8220;As a South Korean idol group, BTS have smashed so many preconceived notions and industry odds to become chart-topping, Grammy-nominated musicians,&#8221; Jeff Benjamin, Billboard&#8217;s K-pop columnist, told AFP.</p>
<p>&#8220;Crucially, they did it not by adjusting their viewpoints, perspectives or languages to cater to the larger market but by firmly establishing themselves as the K-pop musicians they are.&#8221;</p>
<p>What do they do?<br />
Aside from music, the band has long championed global progressive causes, from the Black Lives Matter protests to fighting anti-Asian racism in the United States.</p>
<p>They&#8217;ve spoken at the United Nations and appeared at the White House, while still remaining one of the most popular bands in the world on TikTok, Instagram and Twitter.</p>
<p>Prior to BTS, K-pop &#8220;was treated as a niche interest, separate from global culture&#8221;, Sarah Keith, a senior lecturer in media and music at Australia&#8217;s Macquarie University, told AFP.</p>
<p>&#8220;BTS&#8217;s global popularity has led to a change in this perspective. BTS has arguably changed how the world perceives South Korea.&#8221;</p>
<p>How are they celebrating?<br />
Ironically, the band is currently on a hiatus, with two members performing their mandatory South Korean military service.</p>
<p>All able-bodied South Korean men must serve at least 18 months in the military, and after a years-long debate about whether BTS deserved an exemption, Jin, the oldest member of the group, began his service in December. J-Hope started his service in April.</p>
<p>But the septet released a new digital single last week to celebrate the anniversary: ‘Take Two’, purportedly a nod to the band&#8217;s second chapter after a decade as musicians.</p>
<p>&#8220;All seven members participated in &#8216;Take Two'&#8221;, their agency Hybe said. &#8220;The song conveys their appreciation for ARMY, for all the love you shower them with.&#8221;</p>
<p>A number of important tourist spots across Seoul, including the Namsan Seoul Tower and Dongdaemun Design Plaza, will be lit up in purple &#8212; ARMY&#8217;s colour &#8212; in celebration of the anniversary.</p>
<p>Band leader RM will attend the main event of the celebration in Seoul at the Han River Park on 17 June.</p>
<p>On a break?<br />
The band, which is known to be extremely hard-working and have maintained a relentless pace of new releases in their nine years at the top, said last year they were &#8220;exhausted&#8221; and would take a break.</p>
<p>RM said at the time that the K-pop industry &#8212; known for its cut-throat competition &#8212; was not allowing him to mature as an artist, saying he felt like a &#8220;rapping machine&#8221;.</p>
<p>Since the announcement, BTS members who are still obliged to join the military have focused on their solo careers.</p>
<p>Jimin released his six-track solo album ‘Face’ in March, with the single ‘Like Crazy’ earning him a place in the record books as the first South Korean solo artist to land the number one spot on the top US songs chart.</p>
<p>Band member Suga is currently on his first solo worldwide tour.</p>
<p>What&#8217;s next?<br />
Local media says the ongoing break may last as long as seven years if the septet decides to wait until all members complete their military duties before resuming group activities.</p>
<p>In March, Bang Si-hyuk, chairman of Hybe and the mastermind behind BTS, said industry figures &#8212; including global ratings and album sales &#8212; showed a declining demand for K-pop, blaming the BTS hiatus.</p>
<p>&#8220;It remains to be seen how the group can re-integrate as a seven-member group once they have finished their military service, as this is usually a difficult time for male artist groups,&#8221; Keith said.</p>
<p>But the ongoing break could be &#8220;a growth period for BTS overall as members pursue solo interests and add more diversity to BTS&#8217;s output&#8221;, she added.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://bein.online.mills.edu/10-years-of-k-pop-megastars-bts-five-things-to-know/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Messi says doesn&#8217;t think will play another World Cup</title>
		<link>https://bein.online.mills.edu/messi-says-doesnt-think-will-play-another-world-cup/</link>
					<comments>https://bein.online.mills.edu/messi-says-doesnt-think-will-play-another-world-cup/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bein.online.mills.edu/?p=9</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Lionel Messi on Tuesday confirmed he &#8220;doesn&#8217;t think&#8221; he will play at another World Cup in an interview with Chinese media, after the 35-year-old led Argentina to victory at last year&#8217;s tournament in Qatar. &#8220;I have said several times before that I don&#8217;t think so, that that (2022) was my last World Cup,&#8221; he said]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lionel Messi on Tuesday confirmed he &#8220;doesn&#8217;t think&#8221; he will play at another World Cup in an interview with Chinese media, after the 35-year-old led Argentina to victory at last year&#8217;s tournament in Qatar.</p>
<p>&#8220;I have said several times before that I don&#8217;t think so, that that (2022) was my last World Cup,&#8221; he said when asked by China&#8217;s Titan Sports in a video interview if he might feature at the 2026 tournament in North America.</p>
<p>&#8220;I will see how things go but in theory I don&#8217;t think I will be around for the next World Cup.&#8221;</p>
<p>The seven-time Ballon d&#8217;Or winner is currently in Beijing where Argentina will play a friendly against Australia on Thursday.</p>
<p>His comments come after he said earlier this year to Argentinian newspaper Ole that it would be &#8220;very difficult&#8221; to play at another World Cup.</p>
<p>He will turn 39 during the next tournament.</p>
<p>Messi last week announced he would join MLS side Inter Miami after his two-year deal with Paris Saint-Germain came to an end.</p>
<p>Argentina will play Thursday&#8217;s friendly against Australia at the 68,000-capacity Workers&#8217; Stadium in Beijing.</p>
<p>The match is a repeat of the last-16 tie between the teams at the World Cup in Doha, which Argentina won 2-1.</p>
<p>With Chinese fans desperate to see the former Barcelona star in action, tickets have been rapidly snapped up despite being sold at prices rising to 4,800 Yuan ($671).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://bein.online.mills.edu/messi-says-doesnt-think-will-play-another-world-cup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trump pleads not guilty over classified documents</title>
		<link>https://bein.online.mills.edu/trump-pleads-not-guilty-over-classified-documents/</link>
					<comments>https://bein.online.mills.edu/trump-pleads-not-guilty-over-classified-documents/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[International]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bein.online.mills.edu/?p=6</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Donald Trump pleaded not guilty Tuesday to dozens of criminal counts of mishandling some of the US government’s most sensitive secrets and scheming to prevent their return, in a historic first court appearance as a federal defendant. The former president—and the favourite to fight next year’s election for the Republicans—gave himself up to US Marshals]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Donald Trump pleaded not guilty Tuesday to dozens of criminal counts of mishandling some of the US government’s most sensitive secrets and scheming to prevent their return, in a historic first court appearance as a federal defendant.</p>
<p>The former president—and the favourite to fight next year’s election for the Republicans—gave himself up to US Marshals in Miami for a hearing that set up the unprecedented scenario of a White House race litigated from the courtroom as well as at the ballot box.</p>
<p>On the eve of his 77th birthday, Trump appeared before a magistrate judge to be formally presented with 37 counts under seven charges brought by a special counsel probe that opened after an FBI raid of his Florida mansion 10 months ago.</p>
<p>But he dismissed his prosecution as politically-motivated in a speech to supporters framing the indictment as an effort to interfere in the 2024 election.</p>
<p>“Today we witnessed the most evil and heinous abuse of power in the history of our country. Very sad thing to watch,” Trump said after returning to his summer residence in New Jersey.</p>
<p>The hearing—just weeks after Trump denied state level financial fraud charges in a separate case in Manhattan—came with the former reality TV star’s mounting legal woes threatening to derail his bid to return to the Oval Office.</p>
<p>The US government—which has never before prosecuted a former president—accuses Trump of violating the Espionage Act and other laws when he removed classified documents upon leaving office in 2021 and failed to give them up to the National Archives.</p>
<p>Authorities say he conspired to thwart investigators and knowingly shared national security secrets with people who did not have the requisite clearance.</p>
<p>After the hearing Trump jetted from Miami back to his golf club in Bedminster, New Jersey, where he blamed President Joe Biden for his prosecution.</p>
<p>“A corrupt sitting president had his top political opponent arrested on fake and fabricated charges—of which he and numerous other presidents would be guilty—right in the middle of a presidential election, in which he’s losing very badly,” said Trump, speaking from the front of the clubhouse, at a podium flanked by American flags.</p>
<p>He was cheered by several hundred supporters, including 100 members of a conservative organization of Vietnamese Americans who had donned matching red dresses and chanted: “We love Trump.”</p>
<p>‘Travesty’</p>
<p>Trump enjoys strong backing from Republican voters, 81 percent of whom believe the charges against him are politically-driven, according to a new Ipsos poll.</p>
<p>Antonio Rufa, 30, who had come to Bedminister to support the tycoon, called Trump’s indictment “a travesty” while 57-year-old Vincent Larusso said the prosecution was designed to prevent Trump from running for reelection.</p>
<p>“This is not democracy and people can see this from a hundred miles away,” Larusso told AFP.</p>
<p>The government has recovered more than 300 documents with classified markings from Trump since officials discovered his correspondence with North Korean leader Kim Jong Un was missing, US media reported.</p>
<p>The records were the work of top national security and law enforcement agencies such as the CIA and NSA, according to prosecutors, and some concerned the military and nuclear capabilities of the United States and foreign countries, and “plans for possible retaliation in response to a foreign attack.”</p>
<p>The 49-page indictment, dismissed by Trump as “ridiculous,” includes photographs of boxes of records stacked at Mar-a-Lago, his Palm Beach residence, in a ballroom and in a bathroom and shower.</p>
<p>One image showed that by December 2021, some of the boxes that had been moved to a storage room fell, with their contents spilling across the floor.</p>
<p>‘Don’t play ball’</p>
<p>Trump dismissed his attorneys’ attempts to comply with a subpoena for the return of the records, according to the indictment, which quoted him asking a lawyer: “What happens if we just don’t respond at all or don’t play ball with them?”</p>
<p>The runaway frontrunner in the 2024 Republican primary—Trump leads second-placed Ron DeSantis by more than 30 points—has been impeached twice over allegations of misconduct in office and was recently found liable for sexual abuse.</p>
<p>He faces indictment or ongoing scrutiny in four criminal probes—in Washington, Florida, Georgia and New York—and could find himself on trial in multiple cases as he campaigns to return to the White House.</p>
<p>The pugnacious billionaire has repeatedly complained that the investigations against him amount to a baseless “witch hunt”—and has vowed to stay in the race regardless of the outcome of the documents case.</p>
<p>He said Monday he would appoint a special prosecutor on his return to office to investigate Biden, who is not facing any credible accusations of criminality.</p>
<p>Republican leaders in Congress and Trump’s rivals for the party’s presidential nomination have largely glossed over the gravity of the allegations against him, instead attacking the Justice Department.</p>
<p>Fewer than one per cent of US federal defendants go to trial and win acquittal, according to the Pew Research Centre. The vast majority—around 90 per cent—plead guilty.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://bein.online.mills.edu/trump-pleads-not-guilty-over-classified-documents/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
